window.questionsArray = [
  {
    question: "Orange",
    choices: ["תפוח", "ענבים", "תפוז", "מלפפון"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Dog",
    choices: ["כלב", "חתול", "דג", "ציפור"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Coffee",
    choices: ["תה", "קפה", "מים", "חלב"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Two",
    choices: ["אחת", "שתיים", "שלוש", "ארבע"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Blue",
    choices: ["כחול", "אדום", "ירוק", "צהוב"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Square",
    choices: ["מעגל", "מרובע", "משולש", "פירמידה"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Guitar",
    choices: ["גיטרה", "פסנתר", "תופים", "כינור"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Apple",
    choices: ["בננה", "תפוח", "אננס", "קיווי"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Winter",
    choices: ["קיץ", "חורף", "אביב", "סתיו"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Car",
    choices: ["רכב", "אופניים", "אוטובוס", "רכבת"],
    answer: 0,
  },
];

window.questionsArray2 = [
  { english: "Orange", hebrew: "תפוז" },
  { english: "Dog", hebrew: "כלב" },
  { english: "Coffee", hebrew: "קפה" },
  { english: "Two", hebrew: "שתיים" },
  { english: "Blue", hebrew: "כחול" },
  { english: "Square", hebrew: "מרובע" },
  { english: "Guitar", hebrew: "גיטרה" },
  { english: "Apple", hebrew: "תפוח" },
  { english: "Winter", hebrew: "חורף" },
  { english: "Car", hebrew: "רכב" },
];
